http://www.asashi.com.my/page/privacy-policy

Repair & Services
InformationAbout UsContact UsCareersPayment MethodFAQ & Warranty PolicyPrivacy Policy
03-41617933 | 03-41426688 | 03-41431911| 03-41422486 |012-3590399 |019-3190799  | 019-2466799  |019-2618799  | 012-6434299 | 012-6714299 | 012-2985199
Operation Hours: Mon to Sat ( 9.30am to 6:30pm )      sales@asashi.com.my
Advanced Search
Quick Access
Repair & Services
Asashi Facebook
Asashi Technology
Asashi Gaming
AsashiTech Instagram
AsashiGaming Instagram
Motherboards
Power Supply Units (PSU)
Processors
RAM
Solid State Drive (SSD)
Sound Card
Desktop PCs
Acer
Alienware
Asus
Dell
DIY Package
HP
Audio-Technica
AVF (Gaming Freak)
Cooler Master
Corsair
Creative
Edifier
Florpad
Fnatic Gear
HP
IMPERION
Warlord
Zowie Gear (By BenQ)
Hardware Accessories
Hand Tools/Truck
Screw Driver
Lifestyle and Gadgets
Handheld Gimbal
Baby Monitor
Battery
Car Parking Card
Accessories
(Projector)
Wall TV Bracket
Desk Mounts
Work Station
Tablet Stand
Bracket (Projector)
Cable (Projector)
Document Camera
Presentation Pointers
Projector Controlller
Projector Hardware
Projector Lift
Projector Mobile Stand
Projector Mount
Projector Screen
1. Collected Information
We only collect the informations that needed for the registration procedure at our website or when fill up the registration form on the site.
The information that we gathered are voluntarily submitted by the customers to us. We collect customer's personal information during the account registration on our site on our site.
2. Personal Identification Details
Your personal identification details are used to process your:
•Order of the products
•Customize your profile information
•Internal usage with legal requirements
•Update your status of online shopping in our site
•Update our customers with our latest news of updates/changes, promotions and events.
3. Can I change my shipping address?
Yes. Kindly drop us an email to us at online@asashi.com.my or call us 03-4142 6688 for changing address request.
However, changing of shipping is only applicable if the order has not been shipped out.
4. Changes to our Privacy Policy
Asashi Technology have the rights to do any changes/updates Privacy Policy contents without giving prior notice to the customers. Do keep track on the Privacy Policy page on our website.
5. Security
Our company website do applies appropriate security application in order to prevent the leaking customers' personal identification details from third parties, illegal disclosure and hackers.
However bear in mind that any information transmitted through Internet is NOT 100% guaranteed safe and secure.
Subscribe our Newsletter We will keep you informed about special offers, promotions, exclusive product information and news.
Microsoft Office 365
Official Brand Stores
Copyright © 2019 Asashi Technology Sdn Bhd
Change to Desktop Version
